Thank you for watching!
Hi, I'm Ryo, a subscriber.
Pleased to meet you.
And this is the ZOZO Club channel.
No, no, no.
Oops.
Ah!
Colocolocolocolocolocolocolocolocolocolocolocolocolocolocolocolocolocolocolocolocolocolocolocolocolocolocolocolocol
Wow!
Please announce today's project.
Let's go in.
Nogizaka bowling 2023
Yay!
Oh!
Every year on June 22nd, it's Bowling Day.
So this time
with Bananaman, who loves bowling.
we will hold a bowling tournament
by 22 members this week on June 22.
We will have a preliminary round
and the 6 winners will go to the finals.
Iwamoto, Kubo, and Ogawa are in the Himura team
Tamura, Matsuo, and Sugawara will be
Tamura, Matsuo, and Sugawara will fight on Shimoda's team.
Don't you guys bowling right now?
These two are bowling for the first time today.
Are you kidding me? That's how they're going to win?
How low can they go?
We're doing it for the first time today.
We've done something...
Have you ever tried bowling before, Chokichi?
My grandma loves bowling.
I've been coming to the bowling alley since I was little.
You can count on it.
But when I was in elementary school...
I won a parent-child bowling tournament
I won it once.
Oh, man.
Here, here.
I'm kind of excited about the second semester.
We're going up against each other as a team.
There's a glimpse of the rest of the team back there.
But there's only two of us.
But there's more.
We've still got a couple of guys who made it through the preliminaries.
But those kids are...
For the entertainment for the halftime show.
The sideshow from hell.
It was like they were sent to the sideshow because they lost.
They've been toggling around for about an hour after losing.
They've been tokkumppin' like crazy since about an hour before we lost.
But you know what?
We're not competing in regular bowling this time.
Yes, sir.
Oddballs will bowl as usual.
Those who don't like odd numbers.
You like this?
We're doing this for 10 months?
A year.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
This time, you'll throw 10 frames.
Loose frames are the original game.
The results will determine
Tokyu Handicap will be decided
The winning team will receive
will receive a luxurious gift.
Thank you for watching!
Kimura team's first throw is Mano Iwamoto, who made an excellent spare in the preliminary round.
Wait a minute, wait a minute. Your hand is wrong.
I've been bowling like this. You know, in bowling, you put two in the middle.
No, like this. It's shocking.
Like this? I've been doing it like this. We've all been doing it like this.
Really? You don't bowl that much?
Well, if you don't know how to bowl, I'll just give you the basics.
You hold the bowling ball like this.
Let's try it this way.
Straight ahead, straight ahead.
Eeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee!
You can break your fingers doing that, you know.
Come on, Kimura team!
Come on! Come on!
Yamamoto, go!
I'll do my best, sir.
Come on!
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
It's good to beat them all, isn't it?
Oh, you're good.
That's good.
Go, go, go, go, go.
Oh!
That's good.
Six-pin.
Yes, 6-pin spin.
You've got a great spin.
You're good.
I knew it.
It's still a little bit hard.
It's hard.
This one's the last one left.
That one is hard to get.That one is hard to get.
Yeah.
Good luck with that one
No, this is tough.
But it's big when you get the spare.
This is big.
Here we go.
Go for it!
Go, go, go!
Oh, wow.
Wow.
There's one in the back.
Oh!
It's so hard!
It's on the menu, sir.
Oh no!
Tamra, bowling for the first time in her life, used her softball experience to score a spare in the qualifying round.
Tamura, how did you do that earlier?
Yes, I'm the same type of person.
Wow!
What kind of qualifying did you do?
It's like qualifying!
Good luck!
Straight down the track, course, Tamura!
Go!
Oh, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
There you go!
Oh, it's good!
Yay!
Every day is a strike strike!
Yes!
Here we go!
Tamura gets the first strike of his life
Tamura gets the first strike of his life!
You've got it!
This is strong!
I want it up and down more!
Cute! Cute!
The second frame is an even-numbered frame.
Let's go!
Let's try our luck!
What's that?
Let's try our luck at "Marubatsu"!
If you draw a "round lucky" card, the "round lucky" team is safe.
The "Batsu" team will put on a pot holder and throw it.
Ogawa and Sugawara, who were nominated as the lucky girl of each team, will try their luck in this test.
If they get that one, they both get the next frame!
Oh no, the pot holders are indeed in trouble!
Then, please open them both at once, facing the other way.
I want this place!
I'm scared!
Let's open it up!
Wow!
It's true.
Shokichi.
I knew it!
I'm so nervous.
Mimuya, you must get it.
Oh, man...
Cheer for me!
Congratulations!
We're the stronger team.
Hang in there.
I knew this was gonna hurt.
You're gonna fail.
I'm sorry.
Ignite it before Yuya explodes
Next is Hakuubo
Can you take this spare chance with the control you showed in the qualifying round?
Spare!
Spare, please.
Here we go.
Please, please, please, please
Ok.
Kubo.
Oh, I'm in the middle of nowhere.
I'm in the middle of nowhere.
I'm scared.
I'm going into the middle of nowhere!
You should wipe the ball like this, because you're gonna get oil on it.
And your hands are going to get soaked, so here's the air coming out on the bowling ball.
And then I'll put this on, because it's almost there.
And that's why there's no point in drying it off, and no point in greasing it.
Oh, wait a minute.
It's so hard!
It's absolutely impossible.
turn, turn, turn!
Gaturn!
We have a great chance here to take advantage of the strike that Tamura got and take the lead in points.
Can Shitora grab a chance by grabbing the pot?
Gaturn!
Yes, Gaturn!
Yes, yes, Gaturn!
Yay!
It's hard to throw!It's hard to throw.
Sorry.
He won the parent-child tournament, and scored the highest in the preliminary round. Will he be able to show his skills in the main tournament?
Excuse me, can I get a strike? Next time?
Next time. - Okay. Thank you.
Go for strikes!
Aya!
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
I hit it!
Baguette. Nice, nice.
Come on, Kubo!
Now for the spare
Here we go.
Oh, good.
Good!
You're doing great!
Oh, my God!
I knew it was the one hidden in the back.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
That's totally good.
That's good.
That one's good.
Sugawara, who qualified with the fastest speedball of all the members.
Can he make up for his lack of questioning here?
Let's go! Go for it! Center, center, center!
Let's go! Here we go! Come on!
Oh! That's good!
Fast!
Oh! Oh, yeah!
Oh! Good!
After this, Tamura, who just struck, goes for the spare, but doesn't get it, and the third frame is up!
Let's play another game frame.
Mr. Himura, game name, please.
Foot Pin Standup Showdown
Yay!
Foot Pin-Up Showdown
One representative must use only his or her feet to
to stand four toy bowling pins
time trial to stand up to 4 toy bowling pins.
The losing team
the losing team will be asked to throw the bowling pin in the opposite direction of the puller.
This game is played by
Iwamoto from Himura team
Shimoda team and Matsuo team
I'm counting on you.
Go for it!
I'm scared.
Let's go!
Come on!
Wait a minute, this is so hard!
Oh, great!
It's okay if you've got one foot in front of the other.
I've got to go get it.
What are you doing?
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
Yay, yay, yay.
Come on, come on, come on.
Let's just hurry up, let's just hurry up.
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
Feet, feet, feet, feet
Feet, feet, feet
Come on, come on, come on
I know you can't do this.
I have to stand up again.
Oh, man, I can't stand up on my feet.
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
Catch up, catch up, catch up.
My legs are cramping up.
Yellow, yellow, yellow...
Oh, my God, can I get a pink one when I get there?
Can I get pink?
You can say "get the pink one" if you want.
That's right, that's right, that's right.
Grab it, grab it, grab it, grab it.
Don't knock it down, don't knock it down.
I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared
I can't stand it, I can't stand it, I can't stand it, I can't stand it
I won't be bullied
I won't be afraid, I won't be afraid, I won't be afraid
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry
I'll help you there
Help, help, help
Yes, yes, yes!
Matsuo's gonna do it.
Matsuo's famous for his bad footwork.
Is Matsuo bad? I think so.
Not so good.
He's got bad make-up and everything.
It's not good, Matsuo.
Let's call it a day.
All right.
Let's get started.
Go for it, go for it.
Careful.
Nice.
Ooh.Ooh.
Take your time.
Just take your time.
A little more.
A little bit more.
That's good.
Easy, easy, easy.
Don't knock it over.
That's good.
Careful, careful.
It's okay to get out of the chair.
It's not safe.
Slowly, slowly, slowly.
Too fast.
You know what I'm talking about.
You got this.
Not even close.
You're not very good on your feet, are you?
That's not a problem.
Here's the time... 1:59 for the Himura team.
That's a lot of time.
And ours was 42 seconds.
And now, the Himura team.
We'll have you throw it the other way around.
I'll do it, I'll do it, I'll do it, I'll do it.
Me?
I've never done it before.
But, Mr. Left?
No, that's just Mr. Tompei.
Mr. Nimura, you're pretty good with volume.
He plays golf with his right hand.
But you throw with your left.
Bowling is completely left.
Let's see you throw with your right.
Mr. Himura, please.
So cute!
But...
Not much changed.
It didn't change much, but it's okay.
Scatches are already in place.
See that triangle over there?
Right in the middle of it.
Shut up. The old man's here to teach you.
Shut up, there's an old man here to teach you.
What's with that old guy?
Shut up, old man. He's like a pin.
He looks like a pin.
Draw a red line around my neck.
All right, all right...
That's not "yes, yes"!
Let's go, Kubo.
It's hard, isn't it?
Look at the triangle
Good job!
Oh, no, no, no!
Nice try.
Nice!
Nice
Let's go.
Spark.
Oh, shit.
Oh, no!
Matsuo's spare attempt fails to score, and Kimura's team finishes 4th in the fourth level with 4 pings.
Remember that time when we were father and son?
"That time when we were father and son"?
Remember when we were father and son?
Good luck!
How'd you get it right this time?
Okay.
Oh, shit.
I got it.
Yeah. - Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
Yay!
I don't understand how that thing works.
There's power in this bowling alley.
And it's a girl.
Why is it a girl?
It's one of the most important knives.
It's bad when you have a spare.
It's OK.
It's okay.
One pin left.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
That's a tough one.
It's going to stay.
Kogishi! Let's go for another strike!
Let me see one.
I haven't shown anything good so far.
That's right. You haven't shown anything good.
You...
I'm pulling the trigger.
I'll take the middle.
Yes, sir.
Focus.
You're early. You're early.
Oh, that's nice.
I can't help it.
Powerful girl.Powerful Girl
Oh, no!
Ms. Stara, you're going to get sparked.
Spark! Spark!
Oh, no.
There's pink in the back.
I'm scared. I'm scared.
There you go.
Oh, my God!
I've been sparked!
Here comes Citara with the spark!
She's got a spare on the speedball!
Spark! Spark!
Yes! Spare!
We're halfway through, Mr. Kimura.
Right?
Which means this could be...
It's half-time!
We did it!
What's that? It's like playing with kings.
And here's a little something for all the players.
Yay!
That's great!
Idol radio!
Oh! That's it!
The winner in each category!
The king, actually.
What's this?
I'm going to enjoy a night out while eating this.
That's great.
It's good, it's good, it's good.
Okay, first pair of nightclubs, let's get to it.
Let's get started!
Mr. Yamaken is here! And the two waist men, too!
Yamaken!
Finally! Here they come! This year too!
We did it again this year! Dancing by Mr. Yamaken!
We only have them at the end of the year, but today they came on short notice!
We thought you would not come!
I didn't think you would come this year!
We were afraid you wouldn't see us.
Thank you so much!
We have a stage!
Let's get you to your seats.
Great! That's good!
It's going to be a good start! You're starting with Mr. Yamaken!
It's true!
With the five-term students at your back!
Thank you! Thank you!
I was so nervous because it was a 2-day show!
Koshimoto dancers were great!
Good! Not bad!
They looked good!
The end was great!
They're eating so much!
Today, we would like to announce the members selected for the 33rd single of Nogizaka463!
Every time a new single is released, the members who will perform the song are selected.
Here is the formation of this year's group. 20 members, the same as the previous single.
The first member to be called out was
Lilia Ito
Ito, a third term student, was selected for the first time in 10 years.
"Last time, I was selected as the center of the under group.
To be honest, it was my last chance.
I thought if I didn't make it here, I might not make it.
I was frankly happy to hear my name called for the first time in a while.
I'm the eldest of the third term students.
I hope there's something I can do to help.
The next person whose name was called was
Lennon Nakamura
Nakamura, a third term student, was selected for the first time.
I didn't expect to be selected this time.
I heard it over the phone backstage right after the show.
I was so surprised that I couldn't speak.
Well, I'm sure there are a lot of opinions about it.
I'm sure there will be a lot of opinions, but I'm going to do my best to help Nogizaka in a positive way.
Third row, followed by Yuna Shibata
Ayame Tsudane
Satsuki Sugawara
Sakura Kawasaki
Saya Kanekawa
Nao Yumiki
The last person called up in the third row was
Teru Ikeda.
Ikeda, a 5th term student, was selected for the first time.
It's always the same, but my heart was beating so loud that I couldn't think about anything else.
It was like my heart stopped beating so loud that I couldn't think of anything else, and then it stopped when they called my name.
It was an invaluable experience for me to work as a Wonder member for all the singles.
I think it was an invaluable experience for me.
I will do my best to make the most of this experience.
The reason why I fell in love with Nogizaka was "Nogizaka Kenken-jukyu".
I would be very happy if I could participate in many of these events.
Next is Mayu Tamura from the second row.
Mayu Tamura
Renca Iwamoto Mao Iao
Miku Ichinose Minami Umezawa
Yuki Yoda
Last in the first row: Shiori Kubo
Mizuki Yamashita Sakura EndoMizuki Yamashita Sakura Endo
Haruka Hanaki
And the center of the 33rd single is
Inoue Cleave
Fifth term student Inoue Cleave became the center for the first time.
I thought I had to make sure that I could leave something behind when I was at Axenbotsu.
I've been thinking about it a lot.
It's so frustrating.
By myself.
I'm frustrated that I can't convince myself that I did my best.
That's why I have to work hard.
I want to be a person who can stand there with confidence, even if it's not right now.
I wonder what kind of story the new Nogizaka with Exclusive at the center will tell.
Wait a minute! Wait a minute! I don't know who it is!
I want to guess here. Guess this way.
That's more like it. Right!
Right!
Osaka, Hiroshima and Okinawa Parks go on sale July 1!
Yes, hello everyone. I'm Teresa Ikeda.
Suddenly, I would like to do an impersonation of a certain member. Here I go!
Who is this?
The correct answer is the face that Nao Tomisato makes when asked to make a funny face.
Please subscribe to our channel.